Department of English fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Associations, 1965 - 1979; F-25-8; 11 cm of textual records
  - Association of Universities and Colleges of Canada, 1967; F-25-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 25-14)
  - B.C. Council of Teachers of English, 1965 - 1966; F-25-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 25-14)
  - Canadian Association of American Studies, 1979; F-25-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 25-14)
  - Canadian Linguistics Association, 1965 - 1967; F-25-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 25-14)
  - National Council of Teachers of English, 1965 - 1967; F-25-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 25-14)
  - Philological Association of the Pacific Coast, 1967; F-25-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 25-14)
- Conferences, 1967 - 1979; F-25-9; 13 cm of textual records
  Series consists of materials related to conferences hosted by the Department or attended by faculty members. It includes booklets, correspondence, memoranda, minutes, and reports.
  - Conference of College Composition and Communication, 1967 - 1968; F-25-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - Heritage Festival, 1977; F-25-9-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - Heritage Festival, 1978; F-25-9-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - Heritage Festival, 1978; F-25-9-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - Heritage Festival, 1978; F-25-9-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - Heritage Festival, 1979; F-25-9-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - International Conference on the Teaching of English, 1967; F-25-9-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - World Shakespeare Congress, 1969; F-25-9-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - World Shakespeare Congress, 1970; F-25-9-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
  - World Shakespeare Congress, 1971 - 1973; F-25-9-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 25-15)
- Minutes, 1967 - 1969; F-25-10; 13 cm of textual records
  This set of departmental minutes from 1967-1969 was donated to the Archives by professor and former chair Edgar F. Harden. The minutes document the first democratic procedure for electing a departmental chair at SFU.
  - Minutes 1/3, 1967 - 1969; F-25-10-0-0-1 (Archival box - small 25-16)
  - Minutes 2/3, 1967 - 1969; F-25-10-0-0-2 (Archival box - small 25-16)
  - Minutes 3/3, 1967 - 1969; F-25-10-0-0-3 (Archival box - small 25-16)